Finding aid for the J. Paul Getty Trust Press Releases and Public Outreach Materials, 1954-1959, 1973-2022 (bulk 1983-2022) IA10011
Institutional Records and Archives
- Calendars, 1975-2022; Series IV.; 4.99 Linear Feet (9 boxes); 0.1316 GB (184 files)
  Around 2017 the calendars began to be published in digital format to complement any existing hardcopy versions. The digital calendars are web documents originally published as .html files, and captured here as .mht and .mhtml files. The calendars contain links to the Getty web site which were functional at the time of capture.
  While the number of calendars is extensive, it does not presumed to be a comprehensive collection.
  - The J. Paul Getty Museum:
    - 1970s:
      - December 1975-March 1976 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
      - April-July 1976 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
      - August-November 1976 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
      - December 1976-March 1977 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
      - March-May 1977 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
      - June-August 1977 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
      - September-November 1977 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
      - December 1977-February 1978 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
      - March-May 1978 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
      - June-August 1978 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
      - September-November 1978 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
      - March-May 1979 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - June-August 1979 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - September-November 1979 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - December 1979-February 1980 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
    - 1980:
      - Events, 1980s (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
        includes Third Thursday Concert Series, Four Saturday Drawing Workshops, and Dante Alighieri Society events.
      - March-May 1980 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - June-August 1980 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - September-November 1980 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - December 1980-February 1981 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
    - 1981:
      - March-May 1981 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - June-August 1981 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - September-November 1981 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - December 1981-March 1982 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
    - 1982:
      - April-June 1982 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - July-September 1982 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - October 1982 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - November 1982 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - December 1982 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
    - 1983:
      - January 1983 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - February 1983 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - March 1983 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - April 1983 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - May 1983 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - June 1983 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - July 1983 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - August 1983 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - September 1983 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - October 1983 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - November 1983 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
    - 1984:
      - February 1984 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - March 1984 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - April 1984 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - May 1984 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - August 1984 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
    - 1985:
      - February 1985 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - March 1985 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - April 1985 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - May 1985 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - June 1985 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - July 1985 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - August 1985 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - October 1985 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - November 1985 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - December 1985 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
    - 1986:
      - January 1986 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - February 1986 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - March 1986 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - April 1986 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - May 1986 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - June 1986 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - July 1986 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - August 1986 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - September 1986 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - October 1986 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - November 1986 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - December 1986 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
    - 1987:
      - January 1987 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - February 1987 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - March 1987 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - April 1987 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - June 1987 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - July 1987 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - August 1987 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - September 1987 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - October 1987 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - November 1987 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - December 1987 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
    - 1988:
      - January 1988 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - February 1988 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - March 1988 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - April 1988 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - May 1988 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - June 1988 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - July 1988 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - August 1988 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - September 1988 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - October 1988 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - November 1988 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - December 1988 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - December 1988 (Box 2010.IA.26-83)
      - Summer Lectures and Concerts, July-September 1988 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - Fall Lectures and Concerts, October-December 1988 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
    - 1989:
      - January 1989 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - February 1989 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - February-August, November-December 1989 (Box 2010.IA.26-83)
      - March 1989 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - April 1989 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - May 1989 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - June 1989 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - July-August 1989 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - September 1989 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - October 1989 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - November 1989 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - December 1989 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - Lectures, Winter-Spring 1989 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - Lectures, Winter; Spring 1989 (Box 2010.IA.26-83)
      - Lectures and concerts, Summer 1989 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - Lectures, Fall 1989 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
    - 1990:
      - January 1990 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - February 1990 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - February-December 1990 (Box 2010.IA.26-83)
      - March 1990 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - April 1990 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - May 1990 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - June 1990 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - July-August 1990 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - September 1990 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - October 1990 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - November 1990 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - December 1990 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - Lectures and concerts, Summer 1990 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - Lectures and concerts, Summer 1990 (Box 2010.IA.26-83)
      - Lectures, films and courses, Fall 1990 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
    - 1991:
      - January 1991 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - January-April 1991 (Box 2010.IA.26-83)
      - February 1991 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - March 1991 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - April 1991 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - May 1991 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - June 1991 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - July-August 1991 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - Lectures and courses, Winter-Spring 1991 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - Lectures and courses, Summer 1991 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - Fall 1991 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - Winter 1991-1992 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
    - 1992:
      - Spring 1992 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - Summer 1992 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - Fall 1992 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - Winter 1992-1993 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
    - 1993:
      - Spring 1993 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - Summer 1993 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - Fall 1993 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - Winter 1993-1994 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
    - 1994:
      - Spring 1994 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - Summer 1994 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - Fall 1994 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - Winter 1994-1995 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
    - 1995:
      - Spring 1995 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - Summer 1995 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - Fall 1995 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - Winter 1995-1996 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
    - 1996:
      - Spring 1996 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - Summer 1996 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - Fall 1996 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - Winter 1996-1997 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
    - 1997:
      - Spring 1997 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
      - Summer-Fall 1997 (Box 2019.IA.03-08)
  - This Month at the Getty:
    - 1998:
      - January 1998 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - February 1998 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - March 1998 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - April 1998 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - May 1998 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - June 1998 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - July 1998 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - August 1998 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - September 1998 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - October 1998 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - November 1998 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - December 1998 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
    - 1999:
      - January 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 113)
      - February 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 114)
      - March 1999 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - April 1999 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - May 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 115)
      - June 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 116)
      - July 1999 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - August 1999 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - September 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 117)
      - October 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 118)
      - November 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 119)
      - December 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 120)
    - 2000:
      - January 2000 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - February 2000 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - March 2000 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - April 2000 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - May 2000 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - June 2000 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - July 2000 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - August 2000 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - September 2000 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - October 2000 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - November 2000 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - December 2000 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
    - 2001:
      - January 2001 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - February 2001 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - March 2001 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - April 2001 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - May 2001 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - June 2001 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - July 2001 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - August 2001 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - September 2001 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - October 2001 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - November 2001 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - December 2001 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
    - 2002:
      - January 2002 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - February 2002 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - March 2002 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - April 2002 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - May 2002 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - June 2002 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - July 2002 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - August 2002 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - September 2002 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - October 2002 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - November 2002 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - December 2002 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
    - 2003:
      - January 2003 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - February 2003 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - March 2003 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - April 2003 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - May 2003 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - June 2003 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - July 2003 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - August 2003 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - September 2003 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - October 2003 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - November 2003 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - December 2003 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
    - 2004:
      - January 2004 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - February 2004 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - March 2004 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - April 2004 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - May 2004 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - June 2004 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - July 2004 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - August 2004 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - September 2004 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - October 2004 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - November 2004 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
      - December 2004 (Box 2019.IA.03-11)
  - Getty RE:View:
    - 2004-2005:
      - November-December 2004 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - January-February 2005 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - March-April 2005 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - May-June 2005 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - July-August 2005 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - September-October 2005 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - November-December 2005 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
    - 2006:
      - January-February 2006 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - March-April 2006 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - May-June 2006 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - Summer 2006 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - Fall 2006 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
    - 2007:
      - Winter 2007 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - Spring 2007 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - Summer 2007 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - Fall 2007 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
    - 2008:
      - Winter 2008 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - Spring 2008 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - Fall 2008 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
  - At The Getty:
    - 2004:
      - Fall 2004 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
      - Winter 2004 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
    - 2005:
      - Spring 2005 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
      - Summer 2005 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
      - Autumn 2005 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
      - Winter 2005 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
    - 2006:
      - Spring 2006 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
      - Summer 2006 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
    - 2009:
      - January-February 2009 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
      - March-April 2009 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
      - November-December 2009 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
      - May-June 2009 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
    - 2010:
      - Summer 2010 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
      - Fall 2010 (Box 2020.IA.04-02)
      - Winter 2010 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
    - 2011:
      - Fall 2011
    - 2012:
      - Spring 2012 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
      - Winter 2012 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
    - 2014:
      - Spring 2014 (Box 2019.IA.03-13)
  - Getty at a Glance:
    - 2005:
      - January-February 2005 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - March-April 2005 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - May-June 2005 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
    - 2006:
      - March-April 2006 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - May-June 2006 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
  - Getty 360:
    - 2015 (Box 2019.IA.03-13)
      Contains Summer and Fall issues.
    - 2016 (Box 2019.IA.03-13)
      Contains all issues for the year.
    - 2017:
      - [Digital version]
        Contains all issues published for the year.
      - [Hardcopy version] (Box 2019.IA.03-13)
        Contains Spring and Summer issues
    - 2018:
      - [Digital version]
        Contains January-March and May-December issues.
      - [Hardcopy version] (Box 2019.IA.03-13)
        Contains Spring issue.
    - 2019:
      - [Hardcopy version] (Box 2019.IA.03-01)
        Contains spring, summer and fall issues.
      - [Digital version]
  - What's On and Get Inspired:
    Administrative History
    The event calendar title was changed to What's On in January, 2020 to coincide with the rollout of a new Getty branding initiative. In April 2020, in response to the Covid-19 pandemic, the title was again changed to Get Inspired and began to be issued weekly.
    Access to digital files in 2020.IA.04, 2021.IA.04, and 2022.IA.04 is available online through the link provided in the inventory.
    - 2020
      Contains all issues published during the year: 4 monthly issues (January-April) of What"s On and 39 weekly issues of Get Inspired.
    - 2021
    - 2022
  - Special Events:
    - 1982 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
    - 1983 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
    - September 16-21, 1986 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
- Magazines, reports, and recordings, 1986-1997; 2012-2022; Series V.; 1.76 Linear Feet (4 boxes); 1.078 GB (50 files)
  Magazines are arranged chronologically by year, and within each year by season. Reports are arranged by fiscal year. Recordings are arranged chronologically by accession.
  These magazines document current events, subjects, and topics about the Getty and its programs, and date from 1986 to 1997 and 2012 to 2022. The magazines are written for a general interest audience and are intended to inform and update the public on the activities of the Getty. The name of the magazine has been periodically changed over time, and these titles are reflected in the inventory headings. The collection does not presume to be comprehensive.
  The Getty Magazine is also published in digital (.pdf) format. Some digital versions are included in this inventory.
  The Year in Review was first published as a web page, and captured in this inventory as .mht and .mhtml files, in fiscal year 2019. Links embedded in the web page were functional at the time of capture. The Year In Review replaces the non-financial front-matter sections previously published in the J. Paul Getty Trust Annual Report (which ceased publication after FY2018.) J. Paul Getty Trust Annual Reports published prior to FY2019 appear in IA30020, J. Paul Getty Museum and J. Paul Getty Trust Accounting and Finance records.
  The recordings document Getty public relations events presented by Communications staff and date from 2016 to 2017. Intended to promote public awareness of the Getty and its activities to specific groups, the recordings include press previews, press conferences, and speeches given to invited audiences.
  Access to digital files in 2017.IA.03, 2020.IA.04, 2021.IA.04, and 2022.IA.04 are available online through the links provided in the inventory.
  - Getty Bulletin:
    - 1986-1987:
      - Volume 1 Number 1, Fall 1986 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - Volume 2 Number 1, Winter 1986-Spring 1987 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - Volume 2 Number 2, Fall 1987 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
    - 1988-1989:
      - Volume 3 Number 1, Winter 1987-1988 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - Volume 3 Number 2, Spring-Summer 1988 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - Volume 4 Number 1, Winter 1988-1989 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - Volume 4 Number 2, Spring-Summer 1989 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - Volume 4 Number 3, Fall 1989 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - Volume 5 Number 1, Winter 1989-1990 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
    - 1990-1991:
      - Volume 5 Number 2, Spring-Summer 1990 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - Volume 5 Number 3, Fall 1990 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - Volume 6 Number 1, Winter 1990-1991 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - Volume 6 Number 2, Spring-Summer 1991 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - Volume 6 Number 3, Fall 1991 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - Volume 7 Number 1, Winter 1991-1992 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
    - 1992-1993:
      - Volume 7 Number 2, Spring 1992 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - Volume 7 Number 3, Fall 1992 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - Volume 8 Number 1, Fall 1993 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
    - 1994-1995:
      - Volume 8 Number 2, Spring 1994 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - Volume 8 Number 3, Summer 1994 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - Volume 9 Number 1, Fall 1994 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - Volume 9 Number 2, Spring 1995 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - Volume 9 Number 3, Winter 1995-1996 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
        Volume 9 Number 3
    - 1996-1997:
      - Volume 10 Number 1, Summer 1996 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
      - Volume 10 Number 2, Winter 1996-1997 (Box 2019.IA.03-09)
  - Getty Magazine and Year in Review:
    - 2012:
      - Spring (Box 2016.IA.03-02)
      - Summer (Box 2016.IA.03-02)
      - Winter (Box 2016.IA.03-02)
    - 2013:
      - Spring (Box 2016.IA.03-02)
      - Summer (Box 2016.IA.03-02)
      - Fall (Box 2016.IA.03-02)
    - 2014:
      - Winter (Box 2016.IA.03-02)
      - Spring (Box 2016.IA.03-02)
      - Summer (Box 2016.IA.03-02)
      - Fall (Box 2016.IA.03-02)
    - 2015:
      - Winter (Box 2016.IA.03-02)
      - Spring (Box 2016.IA.03-02)
      - Summer (Box 2016.IA.03-02)
      - Fall (Box 2016.IA.03-02)
    - 2016:
      - Winter (Box 2016.IA.03-02)
      - Spring (Box 2016.IA.03-02)
      - Summer (Box 2016.IA.03-02)
      - Fall (Box 2016.IA.03-02)
    - 2017:
      - Winter (Box 2017.IA.03-03)
      - Fall-Winter
    - 2018:
      - Spring (Box 2018.IA.03-01)
      - Summer (Box 2018.IA.03-01)
      - Fall (Box 2019.IA.03-01)
    - 2019:
      - Winter (Box 2019.IA.03-01)
      - Spring (Box 2019.IA.03-01)
      - Summer (Box 2019.IA.03-01)
      - Fall (Box 2019.IA.03-01)
    - Digital magazines and reports, 2013-2020:
      - 2013-2019
        2013 contains Summer and Fall editions, and 2014-2019 are complete sets (Winter, Spring, Summer, and Fall).
      - 2020
        Contains a complete set (Winter, Spring, Summer, Fall).
      - Year in Review:
        - Fiscal Year 2019
        - Fiscal Year 2020
    - 2021:
      - Getty Magazine
      - Year in Review (FY 2021)
    - 2022:
      - Getty Magazine
      - Year in Review (FY22)
  - Recordings of public relations events:
    - 2016-2017:
      - Dunhuang press preview, May 2, 2016
      - Tsinghua University presentation by Ron Hartwig, March 30, 2017
      - Los Angeles Concierge Association presentation, May 8, 2017
      - UCLA Anderson School of Management visit, July 26, 2017
      - Harold M. Williams [auditorium] PST:LA/LA press conference, September 12, 2017
- Advertising, 1984; 1994-2004; Series VI; .44 Linear Feet (1 box)
  These advertisements document events, initiatives, and products that the J. Paul Getty Trust wished to publicize to the public through media outlets and date from 1984, and 1997 to 2004. These hardcopy advertisements were published in magazines, newspapers, and other print outlets.
  Arrangement
  Advertisements are arranged chronologically.
  - Museum ad, 1984 (Box 2022.IA.04-01)
  - Multicultural Art Print series [MAPS], ca. 1990s (Box 2022.IA.04-01)
  - Visit the Getty, 1991; 2000 (Box 2022.IA.04-01)
  - Performances, 1994; 1997-2004 (Box 2022.IA.04-01)
  - Getty Center opening, 1997-1998 (Box 2022.IA.04-01)
  - Family, 1998-2002 (Box 2022.IA.04-01)
  - Getty Publications, 1998-2003 (Box 2022.IA.04-01)
  - Friday Nights at the Getty, 1999-2001 (Box 2022.IA.04-01)
  - Concerts, 1999-2002 (Box 2022.IA.04-01)
  - Volunteers and docents, 2000-2001 (Box 2022.IA.04-01)
  - Getty Grant Program, 2001-2002 (Box 2022.IA.04-01)
  - Internships, 2001-2002 (Box 2022.IA.04-01)
  - Website, 2001 (Box 2022.IA.04-01)
  - LA Phil Presents, July 2004 (Box 2022.IA.04-01)
  - LA Magazine, August-September 2004 (Box 2022.IA.04-01)
  - Exhibitions, 1998-2004; (2 folders) (Box 2022.IA.04-01)